[Music]
[音乐]
so this talk is about where we're
所以这个话题是关于我们在哪里
pushing the jvm where the JVM seems to
将JVM推送到JVM似乎在哪里
be going whether we push or not we're
不管我们是否推动
where we think we'll be maybe even in 10
我们认为我们甚至会在10
or 20 years it's we're 10 or 20 years
或20年就是10或20年
into the Java ecosystem we think it's
进入Java生态系统，我们认为
got at least that much time left to run
至少还有很多时间可以运行
one of the key ways to preserve and
保存和保护的关键方法之一
extend the job and the mission of the
扩展工作和任务
JVM and Java is to make sure that we're
JVM和Java是为了确保我们
able to do the the jobs that are coming
能够完成即将到来的工作
up in the future and I want to talk
以后我想谈谈
about that today this will be I I'm the
关于今天，这将是我，我是
I'm the architect of the JVM not I
我是JVM的架构师
didn't by no means design all of it but
绝不是全部设计，而是
I'm the current sitting Oracle architect
我是现任Oracle架构师
within the JVM team I've been involved
我参与了JVM团队
with Java since almost the beginning for
自Java几乎开始以来
for about 20 years now
大约二十年了
and so I I want to tell you how it looks
所以我想告诉你它的样子
to me and how it looks to our team and
对我以及我们团队的感觉如何
and some extent how it looks to the open
以及在某种程度上它看起来如何
JDK community I don't speak for the
JDK社区我不代表
whole community I speak for myself and
我为自己和整个社区说话
my team and Oracle but I hope also to to
我的团队和甲骨文，但我也希望
speak for where we as a community want
为我们社区想要的地方说话
to go with this wonderful technology we
配合这项奇妙的技术
enjoy
请享用
however the lawyers instruct me to tell
但是律师指示我告诉
you not to believe a word I say what I
你不要相信我说的话
want to do I want to give you some of
想做我想给你一些
the trends I want to show how we are
我想展示我们的趋势
taking concrete actions today to work
今天采取具体行动
with those trends it is a complicated
那些趋势使它变得复杂
talk I'm going to talk fast I'm going to
说话，我要说话快，我要
I have time for about a minute per slide
每张幻灯片我有大约一分钟的时间
or not much more so here it comes
还是不多，所以它来了
I did not have time to make it shorter
我没有时间把它缩短
as the elegant letter writer said so
正如雅致的信作者所说
this is a snot this is a slide that I
这是一个鼻涕，这是我的幻灯片
enjoyed making a couple years ago for
几年前喜欢
the JVM language summit how many of you
JVM语言峰会上有多少人
have been to a JVM language summit a few
参加过JVM语言峰会
yeah it's a blast it's always a crowded
是的，这是爆炸，总是很拥挤
room full of crazy people who are
房间里充满了疯狂的人
thinking about the next steps for the
考虑下一步的步骤
Java Runtime we had some we we think we
Java Runtime我们有一些我们认为我们
have some long term goals that that will
有一些长期目标
hold up over the next
坚持下一个
or twenty years and so far two years
或二十年，至今两年
into the predictive cycle it seems to be
进入预测周期
working we want the Java Runtime to have
工作，我们希望Java运行时具有
a uniform model we want all of the
一个统一的模型，我们希望所有
pieces of data to feel similar so that
感到相似的数据片段
the things the reflexes you learn to
你所学反射的事物
work with arrays work on values and
使用数组处理值
objects and primitives and methods and
对象，基元和方法以及
types you want to be able to assign
您想要分配的类型
anything to a variable pass anything as
将任何内容传递给变量
a as an argument return anything as a
作为参数返回任何东西作为
result that's sort of a thing you want
结果就是您想要的东西
strong typing that you want a unified
您想要统一的强类型
way to deal with all the disparate
处理所有不同的方式
details of application composition and
应用程序组成的详细信息和
you want all of this to be very
您希望所有这些都非常
efficient in memory you want to be able
您想要的高效内存
to have data layouts that can be made
具有可以进行的数据布局
tuned to be as flat as possible you want
调整为尽可能平整
to have the data to be easy to make and
具有易于制作的数据，
then when you when you decide that it's
然后当你决定
mission-critical that a particular kind
特定类型的关键任务
of data be very compacted very efficient
数据非常紧凑非常有效
you want the cooks to be able to expend
你希望厨师能够消费
the extra effort to tune up that
进行额外的调整
representation in particular although
尽管特别代表
the Java VM and language began as a sort
Java VM和语言开始是一种
of a better better small talk you might
更好的闲聊
say or better C++ you don't want it to
说或更好的C ++，您不希望这么做
be so pointer intensive in order to get
如此集中指针以获取
efficient memory layouts today pointers
当今高效的内存布局指针
are actually a higher cost than they
实际上比他们要高
were 20 years ago and in 20 years it
在20年前，在20年之前
will be an even higher cost probably so
成本可能会更高
we want to be able to have data layouts
我们希望能够拥有数据布局
that are pointer thrifty which is a new
指针节俭是新的
a new direction for Java that was not
Java的新方向
that could not have been predicted 20
无法预料的20
years ago one thing that we always want
多年前，我们一直想要的一件事
is speed and good code computers that
是速度和好的代码计算机
run on bad code well Intel actually runs
运行在错误的代码上，英特尔实际上可以运行
on really bad code but that's amazing
在非常糟糕的代码上，但这太神奇了
how they do it in any case you want you
无论如何，他们如何做到这一点
want code that you're responsible for to
想要您负责的代码
be as as efficiently compiled to the
被有效地编译为
hardware as possible and we want that to
尽可能的硬件，我们希望
continue to be true Java uses online
继续是真实的Java在线使用
optimization techniques which means that
优化技术意味着
it can produce better hot loops in many
它可以在许多情况下产生更好的热循环
cases than static compilers like C and
比静态编译器（例如C和
C++
C ++
the future I think we'll have less
未来我想我们会少
threads in it or more little tiny things
线程或更多小东西
that used to be threads better but are
曾经是更好的线程，但是
more composable and agile so we want we
更易组合和敏捷，所以我们希望我们
want to fire finer grained concurrency
想触发更细粒度的并发
and at the same time less degrees of
同时更少的程度
unimportant freedom to create race
创造种族的不重要自由
conditions in our in our applications so
在我们的应用程序中的条件
I would say the future is post threaded
我会说未来是帖子线程
and so think fibers about that the
因此，请考虑一下
future is also interoperable it is not
未来也是可以互操作的
the case that you can write a language
你可以写一种语言的情况
that is so compelling that everyone will
如此引人注目，每个人都会
drop their existing source code and
删除其现有的源代码并
their existing libraries and go to your
他们现有的图书馆，然后转到
language and code in it for the rest of
语言和其中的代码
their lives right that doesn't work but
他们的生活没用，但是
what you can do is provide a language
你能做的就是提供一种语言
that is really competent to connect
真正有能力连接
those pre-existing components and and
这些预先存在的组件和
take those libraries that you already
拿那些你已经在图书馆
depend on and combine them in new ways
依靠并以新方式将它们结合起来
and make new applications and a language
并开发新的应用程序和一种语言
that does that well well that's going to
那样做的很好
be a language that people use more and
成为人们更多使用的语言
more and and maybe in the end a sizable
更多，也许最终
amount of stuff that will be written in
将要写入的内容数量
it but it will still work with with all
它，但仍然可以与所有人一起使用
the stuff that hasn't been translated
未翻译的东西
into that new languages that sound
听起来的新语言
familiar that's really the story of
熟悉的，这真的是
Java's life it's become a wonderful glue
Java的一生已成为美妙的粘合剂
for applications as well as a something
对于应用程序以及一些东西
for writing new algorithms in its own
自己编写新算法
right and of course you want you want a
对，当然你要
language like Java to be general-purpose
像Java这样的通用语言
you don't want it to be in 20 years we
你不希望它在20年后
don't want to look at Java and say oh
不想看Java说哦
yeah that's the code for writing
是的，这就是编写代码
applications the way they wrote them 20
以他们写的方式应用20
years ago that's no that's not what it
多年前那不是那样
is today today it's a language for
今天是今天的语言
writing modern applications we want it
编写我们想要的现代应用程序
to continue to be like that and finally
继续像那样，最后
one of the jobs of glue is to glue is to
胶水的工作之一是胶水是
hold for more than more than a second
保持一秒钟以上
write glue that lets go after a year is
写一年后放手的胶水是
not very good glue you want if job is
如果工作需要，胶水不是很好
going to be used to glue stuff together
用来将东西粘在一起
you want that glue to last for a long
你想让胶水持续很长时间
time you want it to be library quality
您希望成为图书馆质量的时间
which means that jars that were created
这意味着创建的罐子
20 years ago 30 years ago in the future
20年前30年前未来
should still continue to run I call them
应该仍然继续运行我打电话给他们
dusty jars and give in analogy with the
尘土飞扬的罐子，并比喻
old-fashioned dusty decks right you take
老式的尘土飞扬的甲板就可以了
a dusty deck of Fortran code does it run
一堆尘土飞扬的Fortran代码会运行吗
I don't know it's always an adventure
我不知道这总是冒险
finally whatever the future holds for
最后，无论未来如何发展
new CPU types you know many core wider
您知道更多核心的新型CPU类型
data paths who knows what's coming up
知道即将发生什么的数据路径
persistent memory is a big thing right
持久的记忆是一件大事，对吧
now whatever the new CPUs are we want
现在，无论我们想要什么新的CPU
the JVM and the Java Runtime and the
JVM和Java Runtime以及
Java language team to keep track of that
Java语言团队对此进行跟踪
and be able to compile useful programs
并能够编译有用的程序
efficiently to whatever those new CPUs
高效地应对那些新CPU
are which means we can't just stick with
这意味着我们不能只坚持
64-bit Long's and say that's the end of
64位Long，并说这是结束
all our of all of our primitives it is
我们所有原始的东西都是
hard to forecast but sometimes you can
很难预测，但有时您可以
sort of take a local derivative and make
取当地的衍生品
a make an oversimplified vector in the
使向量中的向量过于简单
direction you think you're going and
你认为你要去的方向，
then maybe when you in the future when
然后也许当你将来
you when you get there you'll say yeah
你到那里的时候你会说是的
that vector was off but it wasn't off by
该向量已关闭，但并没有关闭
too much right that's what you do when
太对了，那是你在做什么的时候
you forecast by the way this is one of
您通过以下方式进行预测：
my two graphics I hope you enjoy it
我的两个图形，希望您喜欢
these slides will be up on on my
这些幻灯片将放在我的
presentation page and openjdk there's a
演示页面和openjdk有一个
link at the end so you're not going to
链接的末尾，这样您就不会
be able to read all this and I'm not
能够阅读所有这些，但我不是
going to be able to explain all of it I
我将能够解释所有这些
in fact I probably have to start going
事实上，我可能必须开始
faster in any case here are some trends
无论如何，这是一些趋势
in JVM design that we are seeing right
在JVM设计中，我们看到的是正确的
now here's here's a attempt at drawing
现在这里是尝试绘制
that vector as it looks at this point in
在这个点上看的那个向量
time we think the predictability and
我们认为可预测性和
security reliability is increasing in
安全可靠性在不断提高
importance we want to be able to create
我们希望能够创造的重要性
JVM packaged applications Java
JVM打包的应用程序Java
applications that can be provisioned in
可以预配的应用程序
advance to do specific jobs and then
提前做一些特定的工作，然后
reliably start up quickly to do those
可靠地快速启动以执行这些操作
jobs and without and consume only a
工作，没有，只消耗一个
predictable amount of resources we want
我们想要的可预测资源量
that resource consumption to be
资源消耗是
manageable we want it to be tunable if
可管理的，我们希望它是可调的，如果
they're going to be GC pauses we want
他们将是我们想要的GC暂停
the the GC pauses to be controllable in
GC暂停以可控制
length this is a this is this is not
长度这是这是这不是
stuff we do today completely well but
我们今天做得很好，但
we're working on it very hard and we've
我们正在努力工作，我们已经
made some progress and over the next
取得了一些进展，接下来
several years we'll be making more
几年我们会做更多
progress in addition we want to be able
另外，我们希望能够进步
to take telemetry out of the
将遥测从
and see what's going on with that VM and
并查看该VM发生了什么情况，并
control it at a distance so you don't
远距离控制它，这样您就不会
have to be up close and personal in a
必须亲密接触
debugger in order to manage it right
调试器以便对其进行正确管理
everybody knows that's the future of how
每个人都知道这就是未来的方向
computing is going in in big data
计算进入大数据
centers so we have a number of logging
中心，所以我们有许多日志记录
capabilities and and remote management
功能和远程管理
capabilities and we're continuing to
能力，我们将继续
invest in those I think that's going to
投资那些我认为这将
be important I already mentioned density
重要的是我已经提到过密度
flatness of data pointer thriftiness
数据指针节俭的平坦度
that's going to be important because
这将很重要，因为
we're putting more and more stuff in
我们正在投入越来越多的东西
memory because memory is just getting
内存，因为内存只是越来越
bigger memory is also getting less
更大的内存也越来越少
uniform memory goes up to terabyte
统一内存高达TB
scales but it's getting slow because
缩放，但它变得越来越慢，因为
it's a special kind of persistent memory
这是一种特殊的持久性记忆
so not only does it live after the
所以它不仅活在
process died but it's also slower to get
进程死了，但获取起来也比较慢
into and out of get data into and out of
进出数据
so we need we need to continue to
所以我们需要继续
provide many size fits many
提供许多尺寸适合许多
opportunities for creating data
创建数据的机会
structures not not a one size fits all
不是所有尺寸的结构都能适合
kind of Lisp or small talk model
Lisp或闲聊模型
immutability is also important
不变性也很重要
immutability is the key to avoiding
不变是避免的关键
those race conditions from unintended
那些意外的比赛条件
unintended degrees of freedom in your
你意想不到的自由度
data structure do you really need that
数据结构您真的需要吗
field to be usable all it is is it's an
可用的领域是
attraction for bugs when you when you
当你当你吸引虫子
hand off something before it's been
在事情发生之前先交出
completely settled to memory and then
完全安定下来再记忆
someone else reads the value reads the
别人读值读
field before you've stored the value in
字段，然后再将值存储在
it or some attacker manages to notice a
它或某些攻击者设法注意到
way to get into that field and put a put
进入该领域并投放的方式
a race condition on it that's just
比赛条件只是
nobody nobody wins from race conditions
没有人没有人从比赛条件中获胜
it's better to reduce degrees of freedom
最好减少自由度
and data structure in particular by
和数据结构，尤其是
locking down immutability everyone
锁定所有人的不变性
understands that that there's not just
知道不只是
one programming language in the world
世界上一种编程语言
the JVM embraces that Java leaves plenty
JVM拥抱Java留下了很多东西
of room for other languages to run
其他语言运行的空间
alongside of it so we want
它旁边，所以我们想要
interoperability and the ability to
互操作性和
choose the language that you want at the
选择您想要的语言
same time we're going to make the best
同时我们要做到最好
language we know how to make - and
我们知道如何制作的语言-
finally this is a trend I think which is
最后，我认为这是一个趋势
important to the creators of the
对创作者很重要
infrastructure of the VM we want to be
我们想要成为虚拟机的基础架构
able to layer our implementations better
能够更好地分层实施
we
我们
want to write so much assembly code we
想写这么多汇编代码
don't want to write so much C++ code
不想写太多的C ++代码
which quite frankly often feels like the
坦率地说，通常感觉像
assembly code we want to be able to
我们希望能够的汇编代码
write stuff in Java and in the
用Java和
higher-level kinds of Java and when I
更高级的Java，当我
say stuff I mean the stuff that actually
说的东西，我的意思是实际上
interprets the Java code so there's a
解释Java代码，所以有一个
real meta-circular bootstrapping problem
真正的元圆自举问题
here but that's it's known how to solve
在这里，但这就是已知的解决方法
that we want to be able to create
我们希望能够创建
abstraction that not only for us but
不仅对我们而且对我们
also our programmers and the compiler
还有我们的程序员和编译器
implementers too to express only what
实施者也只表达什么
they need to in the byte codes without
他们需要在字节码中没有
creating enormous amounts of boilerplate
创造了大量的样板
code at the bytecode level just like at
字节码级别的代码，就像在
the source code level we're kind of
我们的源代码级别
allergic to boilerplate we like ID use
对样板过敏，我们喜欢使用ID
to help us expand it we want the VM to
为了帮助我们扩展它，我们希望VM
be able to expand boilerplate at the at
能够在处扩展样板
the bytecode level invokedynamic is an
字节码级别invokedynamic是一个
example of that we want to we want a
我们想要的例子，我们想要一个
data model that's more flexible uniform
更加统一的数据模型
that's value typed and then finally for
输入值，然后最后
implementing the JVM on top of its own
自己实现JVM
language we're very excited by them by
语言，我们对他们感到非常兴奋
newer technologies like crawl which
较新的技术，例如抓取
allow you to have a complete code
允许您拥有完整的代码
pipeline that's written in Java
用Java编写的管道
portable job all right some big ideas
随身携带的工作好一些大创意
that relate to these trends what the
与这些趋势有关的
platform should be interoperable with
平台应与
other nearby platforms
附近的其他平台
let's make native code and data look
让我们看一下本机代码和数据
like Java code and data not that we can
就像Java代码和数据一样，我们不能
make all the differences disappear but
使所有差异消失，但
let's bring them together let's heal the
让他们在一起，让我们治愈
rift let's let's not force programmers
让我们不要强迫程序员
to leave the Java ecosystem in order to
离开Java生态系统以便
get a tight loop over here or a flat
在这里或公寓得到一个紧密的循环
data structure over here or an off
此处或关闭的数据结构
buffer over here this is why I'm safe
这就是为什么我很安全
was introduced years ago to allow people
是在几年前引入的
not to have to leave the Java ecosystem
不必离开Java生态系统
in order to get to native memory we have
为了进入本机内存，我们有
better replacements for unsafe such as
更好的替代品，例如
project Panama which which lets you get
巴拿马项目，让您得到
a native data in a type safe manner in
以一种类型安全的方式存储本机数据
any case the big idea is to not force
无论如何，大主意是不要强迫
people to go out of the managed runtime
人们离开托管运行时
in order to do manage things we talked
为了管理事情，我们聊了
about this at the boss last night for
昨晚在老板那里
Panama this this is this depends partly
巴拿马这是这部分取决于
on value types because Java's classes
在值类型上，因为Java的类
are currently tied to Java objects and
当前绑定到Java对象，并且
would think the classes are inherently
会认为课程本质上是
tied to objects but they're not a class
与物体捆绑在一起，但它们不是一类
is a bunch of named API points methods
是一堆命名的API点方法
and and data connections fields if you
和和数据连接字段，如果您
will
将
interfaces that has nothing to do with
与无关的接口
objects necessarily in particular the
对象必定特别是
piece of the object that a class does
类所做的对象的一部分
not entail is the identity and
与身份无关
statefulness of the object you can have
您可以拥有的对象的状态
perfectly good classes that are not
完美的课程，不是
stateful and that's exactly what we're
有状态的，这正是我们
doing with value types in project
处理项目中的价值类型
Valhalla we're creating we're creating
瓦尔哈拉我们正在创造我们正在创造
values that do not have the the
没有的值
overheads and burdens associated with
与之相关的间接费用和负担
objects which is headers and pointers
标头和指针的对象
and state and race conditions and yet
以及州和种族条件
have all the other advantages of them
具有其他所有优点
and this will let us have small
这会让我们有小
lightweight agile data types that can
轻量级的敏捷数据类型，可以
then be used as cursors into other parts
然后用作其他部分的游标
of the world in other words smart
换句话说，世界的智慧
pointers in C++ you call them smart
C ++中的指针，您称它们为智能指针
pointers a smart pointer is a little
指针智能指针有点
struct right that you can easily work
您可以轻松工作的结构权
with it has its own invariants and its
它有自己的不变式
own behavior that that's something we
自己的行为就是我们
can do in Java too and that's one of the
也可以用Java来做，这是其中之一
that's one of the outcomes of valhalla
那是瓦尔哈拉的结果之一
will give us ways to describe not state
会给我们描述不状态的方法
that is owned by the Java heap but non
由Java堆拥有，但不是
state that points intelligently
指出聪明地指出
somewhere else in the universe
宇宙中的其他地方
interoperability also depends on a way
互操作性还取决于一种方式
to bridge from Java code to native code
从Java代码过渡到本机代码
to
至
non non Java layouts and the JIT is a
非非Java布局，而JIT是
great code generator for this there's
很棒的代码生成器
nothing that says that the Java jet has
没有什么表明Java喷气机有
to generate code only for working with
生成仅用于
with Java data structures it's a
与Java数据结构
perfectly general code generation
完美的通用代码生成
mechanism it's comparable in power to to
它的力量堪比
other code generators like the GCC back
其他代码生成器，例如GCC back
end or LLVM so let's use it for that
结束或LLVM，因此我们将其用于
this would enable coupling to a wider
这将使耦合到更广泛
range of hardware types data types and
硬件类型范围，数据类型和
in order to in order to have a if we get
为了有一个如果我们得到
a more a better interoperability story
更好的互操作性故事
which is which is what Panama is is
这就是巴拿马
aiming at the project Panama then we'll
针对巴拿马项目，我们将
be able to write in Java code that
能够用Java代码编写
natural and java-like and be able to
自然且类似于Java并能够
work with some Java IDE s Java strong
与某些Java IDE的Java强强合作
typing Java encapsulation and yet still
键入Java封装，但仍然
have smart pointers that point to dusty
有指向灰尘的智能指针
deck COBOL images or cutting-edge GPU
甲板COBOL图像或尖端的GPU
arrays and be able to get in there and
阵列，并能够进入那里，
do the job without without leaving the
在没有离开的情况下完成工作
comforts of Java one I want to call out
Java调用的舒适性
in particular is we have something which
特别是我们有一些东西
I call an as in statement for Java
我称Java为as in语句
that's being prototyped in which you can
在原型中，您可以
make a method handle I hope you have
做一个方法，我希望你有
heard of method handles which
听说过方法句柄
encapsulate a single instruction that
封装一条指令
has a little bit of information to tell
有一点信息要告诉
the JIT which registers that instruction
注册该指令的JIT
uses and otherwise just tells the JIT
使用，否则只是告诉JIT
drop this instruction in when I call
我打电话时放下这条指令
this method handle so it really is a
这个方法可以处理
NASM statement for Java and we have in
Java的NASM声明，我们在
combination with some other technology
与其他技术结合
some Intel engineers are doing really
一些英特尔工程师确实在做
brilliant work creating really nice easy
出色的工作创造了非常好的轻松
to use Java API s for directly coding
使用Java API进行直接编码
vector loops and this is in my opinion
向量循环，这在我看来
the best current way to code vector
当前编码矢量的最佳方法
loops on Intel you I've done it with
你已经在英特尔上循环了
assembly language and with the new CC
汇编语言和新CC
intrinsics but but this is nicer so
内在函数，但是这样更好
panama is broadly speaking i've
泛泛地说，我已经
mentioned a couple times
提到了几次
it's the interconnection story it's what
这是互连的故事
comes after J and I it's the much wider
紧随J，而我则更广泛
broader freeway between the manage in
管理之间的更广泛的高速公路
the end managed world as opposed to the
最终管理的世界，而不是
red-tape ridden narrow footpath that
红带缠着狭窄的小径
j'ni is one of the goals is that we have
j'ni的目标之一是，我们拥有
zero handwritten code last night Paul
昨晚保罗的零手写代码
Santos did a wonderful demo of this
桑托斯对此做了出色的演示
where he showed an API that was a C API
他展示了一个C语言API
with a header file and in a dynamically
与头文件，并在动态
linked library
链接库
he ran the header file to a header file
他将头文件运行到头文件
grovel or called J extract it extracted
grovel或称为J提取它提取
metadata the metadata was about six
元数据元数据大约是六个
kilobytes in size it was in the format
格式为千字节
of a jar which was a bunch of interfaces
一个罐子是一堆接口
real interfaces you could put in your
您可以放入您的真实界面
IDE and look at with annotations about
IDE，并查看有关以下内容的注释
binding and and then fed that into a
绑定，然后将其输入到
bind
绑定
that created classes under the
在
interfaces that were that could connect
可以连接的接口
immediately to the data and code of the
立即将数据和代码
C API and it was a ordinary non-trivial
C API，它是普通的非凡的东西
C API with dozens of data structures and
具有数十种数据结构的C API和
dozens of function entry points and
数十个功能入口点和
pointers and care stars and all that
指针和护理之星等
stuff floating around it wasn't
周围没有漂浮的东西
precondition to work with Java and by
使用Java的前提条件
the way if you do this the old j'ni way
如果您按照旧的j'ni方式进行操作
you have 10 kilobytes of of stuff and
你有10 KB的东西
it's not stuff that's automatically
不是自动的东西
generated by an extractor you had to
由提取器生成的，您必须
write every byte of it it was Java code
写它的每个字节都是Java代码
and C bindings for the Java code in the
和C绑定中的Java代码
native functions and that's no fun you
本机功能，这没什么好玩的
also get with with this new approach you
也可以使用这种新方法
get the directly optimizable calls which
得到直接可优化的电话
I mentioned earlier you get direct
我刚才说过你直接
optimizable access to off heap
可优化访问堆外
equivalent to what you would get from
等同于您将从中得到的
unsafe but it's all type safe and and
不安全，但都是安全的，并且
managed for you you also get storage
为您管理也可以获得存储
management abstractions that help you
可以帮助您的管理抽象
avoid dangling pointers that is a
避免悬空指针是
problem with C and then finally the
C的问题，然后最后
direct access that I mentioned earlier
我之前提到的直接访问
the jumbo data types like 256 bit vector
像256位向量这样的巨型数据类型
in like things those will those are one
在类似的事情中那些将是一个
of the reasons we're doing value types
我们做价值类型的原因
in Java in project Valhalla so that we
Java在Valhalla项目中，这样我们
can interoperate very directly with
可以直接与
whatever data types a a CPU throws at us
CPU抛出的任何数据类型
even if they're greater than 64 bits in
即使它们大于64位
size and that cool in in the end we want
大小，最后我们想要酷
to provide better glue better use of
提供更好的胶水更好地使用
native resources anything outside of the
本地资源
managed runtime of Java another big idea
Java托管运行时的另一个好主意
I already mentioned but I won't expand
我已经提到过，但我不会扩展
on is Java on Java
on on Java是Java
let's implement the Java stack on top of
让我们在以下基础上实现Java堆栈
Java let's reduce our dependency on
Java让我们减少对
assembly code and C and C++
汇编代码以及C和C ++
especially since C++ is moving in its
特别是由于C ++正在
own direction with its own kind of
自己的方向与自己的
managed runtime good luck to them but we
托管运行时祝他们好运，但我们
want to use our runtime this is a kind
想使用我们的运行时，这是一种
of a another unification move and in
另一个统一的举动
particular we want to reduce the cost of
特别是我们想降低成本
ownership for crucial Java technologies
关键Java技术的所有权
starting with the VM but also
从虚拟机开始，但也
other things I depends partly on Panama
我要部分依赖巴拿马的其他事情
itself because parts of the VM will
本身，因为虚拟机的一部分将
always be in see or Hardware sensitive
始终处于可见状态或对硬件敏感
and so will always need some way to get
所以总是需要一些方法来获得
from whatever the rest of the VM is
无论其他虚拟机是什么
coded in Java to the native parts the
用Java编码到本机部分
hardware parts but we want to be able to
硬件零件，但我们希望能够
integrate more and more pieces of Java
集成越来越多的Java
such as Grall into hotspot this depends
例如Grall进入热点，这取决于
also partly on hardware level data
也部分涉及硬件级别的数据
structures which means Valhalla with the
意思是瓦尔哈拉的结构
flat data and the small value types this
固定数据和小值类型
will reduce all of our costs to code in
将减少我们所有的代码编写成本
our own language instead of in C++
我们自己的语言而不是C ++
currently the whole JDK well that's an
目前整个JDK以及
exaggeration but 99% of the jdk is coded
夸张，但99％的jdk已编码
in Java so that's good it's been true
在Java中，这很好，这是事实
for 20 years the method hadn't run time
20年来该方法没有运行时间
was initially coated in an assembly code
最初被涂上了汇编代码
boy that was a mistake that was my
男孩，那是我的错误
mistake
错误
I had to undo it and code it in Java
我不得不撤消它并用Java编写代码
instead and it's much more manageable
相反，它更易于管理
some of us lived through the teething
我们中有些人过着磨牙的生活
pain of that the the t compiler is
äôt编译器的痛苦在于
actually an application of Gras which is
实际上是Gras的一个应用
to generate code statically for Java how
为Java静态生成代码
many of you know there's a head of time
你们中的许多人都知道时间的流逝
compiler in Java 9 oh good yeah ok it's
Java 9中的编译器哦，是的，很好，是的
it's so it's well well publicized there
所以在那里很好地宣传了
are other experiments we're doing we're
是我们正在做的其他实验
using golf the labs are using growl for
使用高尔夫，实验室正在使用咆哮声
a JIT they've been doing that for years
他们一直这样做的准时化
and it's looking very good it's not yet
而且看起来还不错，还没有
ready to replace the server compiler but
准备替换服务器编译器，但是
it will get there other experiments like
它会在那里进行其他实验，例如
the substrate VM Java and Java needs a
底层VM Java和Java需要
project it needs a unifying project in
项目需要一个统一的项目
the open JDK ecosystem and this is a
开放的JDK生态系统，这是一个
this is a working title for you project
这是您项目的工作名称
metropolis there's no formal call for
大都市没有正式呼吁
project yet we're not ready to put the
项目，但我们还没有准备好将
pieces together but I envision a city of
拼在一起，但我设想一个城市
tomorrow called metropolis you you may
你明天可能会成为大都市
know the Fritz Lang movie the Fritz Lang
认识弗里茨·朗（Fritz Lang）电影
movie by the way that the theme of that
电影的那个主题
was also healing a sort of a rift
也治愈了某种裂痕
between the heart and the head or
在心脏和头部之间或
something like that something
像那样的东西
sentimental but given that we're doing
感伤的，但考虑到我们正在做
heal the rift moves in Java unification
治愈Java统一中的裂痕
metropolis the city of the future is
大都市未来的城市是
a bad reference the idea here is to have
一个不好的参考，这里的想法是
an experimental clone of JDK 10 that
JDK 10的实验克隆
hosts extensions work on the t
主持äôt上的扩展程序
compiler and Grall in particular since
特别是因为编译器和Grall
t is built on top of gras we have a
äôt建立在鹅肝的基础上
synergy there but we also want to a ot
协同作用，但我们也想
grow itself in a restricted mode which
在受限模式下成长
which will make it a replacement for the
它将替代
C++ code of the of the current server
当前服务器的C ++代码
compiler in order to do that we need to
为了做到这一点，我们需要
probably define something like a system
可能定义类似系统的东西
Java which is amenable to static
适用于静态的Java
compilation and reduction so we'll be
编译和归约，以便我们成为
able to we'll have to do experiments
能够做实验
with substrate VM style deployment
使用基板VM样式部署
substrate vm is a is a another labs
基板vm是另一个实验室
project that you can see christian
你可以看到基督教的项目
Bimmer work works on it and you can see
Bimmer工作在上面，您可以看到
a JVM language Summit talk from last
最后的JVM语言峰会演讲
summer on that it's called one via one
夏天被称为一一
VM to one compiler to rule them all
VM到一个编译器来全部统治
something like that it's one of those
像这样的东西之一
sorts of titles oh hold on a gap there
各种各样的标题哦，在那儿保持差距
we go so in addition to replacing the
我们除了更换
JIT with with java coded stuff the JIT
JIT与带有Java编码的东西
is the largest piece of the VM right now
是目前最大的虚拟机
it's like I don't know 40% of the VM or
就像我不知道40％的VM或
more it's a huge amount of complicated
更复杂的是
C++ code I'd rather have a huge amount
我宁愿有大量的C ++代码
of complicated Java code it's got to be
复杂的Java代码必须
complicated it's an empty complete
复杂，这是一个空的完整
problem but at least I want to code it
问题，但至少我想编码
in a high-level language but for
用高级语言，但是
teething exercises or or starter finger
出牙练习或初学者手指
exercises we want to do some smaller
我们想做一些较小的练习
pieces the VM also in Java and so
也用Java分割VM等
there's a list of possibilities of P of
有一个P的可能性列表
discrete parts of the VM of the Java
Java VM的离散部分
Runtime that could be transformed from
可以从
C++ into system Java but the big one is
C ++进入系统Java但最大的是
of course growl growl is a very good
当然咆哮是非常好的
code generator as I said earlier on and
如我之前所说的代码生成器和
it should replace c2 eventually but it
它最终应该替换c2，但是它
should also replace c1 which is the
还应该替换c1
client compiler should also replace the
客户端编译器也应替换
interpreter generator and various stub
解释器生成器和各种存根
generator in other words why have
换句话说，发电机为什么
multiple code generators in our
我们的多个代码生成器
ecosystem you know maybe there's some
你知道的生态系统也许有一些
foreign code generation code generator
外码生成码生成器
off on the side that you use for
在您使用的一侧
specialized purpose but if you're
专业的目的，但如果你是
generating stuff that's for the middle
产生用于中间的东西
of the Java stack
Java堆栈
it should be generated by something we
它应该是由我们产生的
control ultimately I twenty years from
最终控制了我二十年
now there might be zero C code in the in
现在in中可能有零个C代码
the in the Java Runtime except for stuff
Java Runtime中的东西
that's edge edge code to connect to C
这是连接到C的边缘边缘代码
api's this will be tomorrow's reference
api的这将是明天的参考
implementation and it'll be a better
实施，它将是一个更好的
reference implementations today than
今天参考实施
today's because when you refer to it for
今天是因为当你提到它
reference you will refer to high-level
参考，您将参考高级
Java code that is easier to understand
易于理解的Java代码
and then C code and assembly code here's
然后是C代码和汇编代码
another big idea I mentioned it earlier
我之前提到的另一个大想法
what's after threads
线程之后是什么
I think of threads as dinosaurs that
我认为线像是恐龙
like dinosaurs they are very heavy and
像恐龙一样，它们非常沉重，
big they usually move slowly they're
大他们通常会慢慢移动
kind of dumb or rather there is some
有点愚蠢，或者说有些
intelligence there but it's like in a
那里的情报，但是就像
little tiny brain in the current stack
当前堆栈中的小脑
frame that's what's going on all the
框架就是所有的一切
other parts of the thread are just stack
线程的其他部分只是堆栈
frames and other metadata that's waiting
框架和其他正在等待的元数据
for you to get done doing the important
让您完成重要的工作
thing that you're doing and it's it's a
你正在做的事情是
cost that you have to pay even though
即使您必须支付的费用
all the all the useful stuff is going on
所有有用的东西都在继续
and just one a few little cache lines
还有一些缓存行
near the top of the stack so let's let's
靠近栈顶，让我们
take those important parts and keep them
把那些重要的部分保留下来
let's throw away the gigantic
让我们扔掉巨大的东西
pre-allocated stack frame
预分配堆栈帧
let's throw away by the way if it's not
如果不是的话，我们就扔掉
just it's not just reallocated stack
不仅仅是重新分配堆栈
segments it's also the pre-allocated
细分也是预先分配的
register files there's tens of kilobits
注册文件有几十千位
of State in modern processors for
现代处理器中的状态
threads and if you when you swap between
线程，如果您之间进行交换
threads you have to load and store
您必须加载和存储的线程
copies of that state get it out of your
该状态的副本会将其从您的
processor and then get a new new
处理器，然后获得新的
snapshot into your processor that's part
快照到您的处理器中
of the dinosaur mentality what we want
我们想要的恐龙心态
is to be able to have pieces of
能够拥有
concurrent execution call themselves
并发执行自行调用
almost call each other almost as
几乎互相称呼为
efficiently as function calls right it's
当函数调用正确时
an old idea
一个老想法
it's called co-routines or fibers but in
它被称为协程或光纤，但是在
any case we don't want to simulate that
任何情况下我们都不想模拟
with gigantic threads anymore so we want
有了巨大的线程，所以我们想要
to leave them behind with the fossils
留下化石
this depends on some really tricky cuts
这取决于一些非常棘手的削减
in the JVM because the JVM has been
在JVM中，因为JVM已经
designed in a threaded model
以螺纹模型设计
it's hard to decouple it and and wean it
很难将其解耦并断奶
off of the thread model but we have some
线程模型，但我们有一些
very good insights into how to do that
关于如何做到的很好的见解
there have been talks in recent years in
最近几年有在
the jvm language summit on how to do
jvm语言峰会上的方法
this library work is also required it at
这个图书馆的工作也需要
all the edges where you could block
所有可能阻塞的边缘
you're assuming that you've got a thread
你以为你有一个线程
that can hang around forever you know in
可以永远徘徊在你所知道的
the in the Tar Pits until you're done
在焦油坑中直到完成
blocking and then wake up and pull
阻止然后醒来拉
itself out of the tar and lumber over
本身脱离了焦油和木材
and do something else that's no good
并做其他不好的事情
instead you want a blocking API to say
相反，您希望阻止的API说
okay I'm blocked put this little tiny
好吧，我被挡住了
piece of important data on the heap and
堆上的重要数据
go do something else that's mean while
去做别的意思
that's useful
这很有用
no no lumbering dinosaurs will still
没有笨拙的恐龙仍会
need something like threads but
需要类似线程的东西，但是
basically one threat one thread will run
基本上一个威胁将运行一个线程
any number of fibers sequent you know in
您知道的任何数量的纤维顺序
a multiplex manner and that's how you
多种方式，这就是您的方式
get huge concurrency wins that's what
获得巨大的并发成功
that's what fiber like or gogo has
这就是像gogo那样的纤维
fibers are called go routines and Co
纤维被称为go例程和Co
routines but basically when you have
例行程序，但是基本上
lightweight deep bits of computation
轻量级的深度计算
decoupled from the heavy threads and the
从繁重的线程和
threads become draft animals and the
线成为草稿动物，
fibers become the intelligent little
纤维成为智能小
thinking dinosaur Raptors or human
思维恐龙猛禽或人类
beings that are that are writing on top
在上面写的存在
of the dinosaurs and I can jump off them
恐龙，我可以跳下
when they get stuck in the mud so
当他们陷入泥巴中时，
mounting and dismounting is the way I
安装和拆卸是我的方式
like to think about fibers so we're
喜欢考虑纤维，所以我们
doing current experiments for for more
做更多的当前实验
intelligent writing on threads one of
在线程上智能编写之一
them is better stack walking there's a
他们最好走栈，有一个
stack walk API which which reifies the
栈漫步API
stack and is able to see inside of it
堆栈并能够看到它的内部
and we want to eventually be able to not
我们希望最终能够
only look at the stack but also replace
只看堆栈也要更换
it say hey I don't like the stack you're
它说嘿，我不喜欢你那堆
running I have a better idea
跑步我有一个更好的主意
run this stack instead I've saved
运行这个堆栈，我已经保存了
whatever I cared out about from the
无论我关心什么
previous stack trust me to come back to
以前的堆栈相信我可以回到
it right now I want you to view this
现在，我要您查看
stuff basically more steerable dinosaurs
恐龙基本上更易于操纵
again lots of library work is required
再次需要大量的图书馆工作
and there's interactions of
并且有相互作用
synchronization which are wonderful
同步很棒
research projects
研究项目
pardon me while I do a time check I
我做一次检查时请原谅我
don't have a clock visible to me okay
我看不到时钟好吗
in any case the the JVM has new tricks
在任何情况下，JVM都有新的技巧
it needs to learn in order to do this it
它需要学习才能做到这一点
needs to be able to take the useful part
需要能够发挥有用的作用
of a computation and and lay it down
计算并放下
dismounted onto the heap which means
卸下到堆上，这意味着
right sizing and right typing the the
正确的大小和正确的输入
stack framed information right now we do
现在就堆栈框架信息
that really well inside of stack frames
在堆栈框架内真的很好
but we don't have the trick of moving it
但是我们没有办法移动它
into the heap dismount and then moving
进入堆下马然后移动
it back when you want to execute it into
当您想将其执行到
the stack remount but that's those are
堆栈重新安装，但那是
tricks we know how to we know how to
技巧，我们知道如何知道
create another big idea is value types
创造另一个大想法是价值类型
everybody's heard of this this is
每个人都听说过这是
another heal the rift classes versus
另一个治愈裂谷类
primitives invidious choice between them
他们之间的原始选择
how am I going to choose between a list
我将如何在列表之间进行选择
and an array event oh no one's good
还有一个数组事件哦，没人好
sometimes the other is good at other
有时对方擅长对方
times they each have their disadvantages
他们每个人都有自己的劣势
let's make them look more the same the
让他们看起来更一样
idea is to distinguish legacy types
想法是区分传统类型
which we call L types because of the
之所以称为L型
letter in the descriptor from new cue
新提示的描述符中的字母
types which will have the cue letter in
带有提示字母的类型
the descriptor the idea is that L types
描述符的想法是L类型
and Q types are very similar they're
和Q类型非常相似
both class based but only the L types
都基于类，但仅L类型
are objects they're the q types are pure
是对象，它们是q类型，是纯净的
values and so this will let us say int
值，所以这可以让我们说int
integer either way they're they look the
不管是哪种方式，它们都是整数
same you can you can write your code you
同样你可以写你的代码
can refactor between int and integer
可以在int和integer之间重构
much more easily the value proposition
价值主张更容易
for Q types is that codes like a class
对于Q类型来说，代码就像一个类
it works like an int it's not an object
它像int一样工作，不是对象
it's a value but you get all your clasp
这是一个价值，但你全力以赴
comforts so you can do encapsulation and
舒适，所以您可以封装和
methods and so forth it depends on Val
方法等等取决于Val
how I depends on many things in order to
我如何依靠很多事情
get this right one thing is we need
得到正确的一件事是我们需要
what's called parametric polymorphism we
所谓的参数多态
need to be able to have lists of int and
需要能够拥有int和
have it work finally that's going to be
终于可以了吗？
good right basically what it boils down
好的权利基本上可以归结为
to is right now we know how to do lists
到现在，我们知道如何做清单
of any L type because L types really
任何L型的，因为L型真的
look all the same to the BM the two
两者看起来都一样
types look different they have different
类型看起来不同他们有不同
sizes and layouts so we need to be able
尺寸和布局，因此我们需要能够
to do the trick of lists and arrays and
做列表和数组的技巧
other things that that are containers
容器的其他东西
for these variably laid out values but
这些可变的价值观，但
it gets you to flat data and more
它可以让您获取平面数据等
efficient use of memory in order one of
有效使用内存以使以下其中一项有效
the technical requirements for pyramid
金字塔的技术要求
polymorphism is that classes behave
多态性是类的行为
somewhat like C++ templates and that
有点像C ++模板，
each template once you give it template
每个模板一旦您给它模板
arguments it turns into a not another
论点变成另一个
class but a species of that class and so
类，但该类的一个物种等等
you have a class that's generic and then
你有一个通用的类，然后
you have many species one for each type
你有很多种类，每种类型一个
argument this again like like fibers
再像纤维一样争​​论
requires deep cuts to the JVM this I
需要对JVM进行深入研究
would say is our biggest big-ticket item
会说这是我们最大的大项目
and hopefully these are the last types
希望这些是最后的类型
we'll ever need or the last way of
我们将永远需要或最后的方式
making types object types are great for
使类型对象类型非常适合
simulation these are much much less
模拟这些要少得多
overhead 'fl more direct non simulation
间接费用'fl更直接的非模拟
of values the impact of this will be
价值的影响将是
comparable to to impact some other major
相当于影响其他一些主要
language features like generics and
语言特性，例如泛型和
lambdas but the important thing is it
lambdas，但重要的是
codes like a class so a few more notes
像一个类的代码，因此还有一些注意事项
on parametric polymorphism that what
关于参数多态性
what it really does it lets you say this
它真正的作用是让你这样说
code see this code this code works for
代码，请参阅此代码，此代码适用
all values not just references to
所有值不只是引用
inherit from a certain interface but int
从某个接口继承但int
and doubles and complex numbers which I
以及双打和复数
haven't invented yet and quaternions
还没发明四元数
which I haven't invented yet this
我还没有发明这个
algorithm works for all of them that's a
算法适用于所有这些
very good thing right we've used that in
很好，我们已经在
C++ with templates it's very powerful it
带有模板的C ++非常强大
will be perhaps even more powerful in
也许会在
Java but you'll be able to build all
Java，但您将能够构建所有
sorts of interesting things on it on it
关于它的有趣的事情
at the same time like the cursors that I
同时像我的游标
mentioned earlier into off heap data
前面提到的成堆数据
structures that will be those should not
那些不应该的结构
be objects those should be values a type
是对象，应该是值，类型
variable is the key actor in parametric
变量是参数化中的关键角色
polymorphism a type variable says I'm as
多态性类型变量说我是
placeholder for a type but I don't know
类型的占位符，但我不知道
what I am yet I don't even know how big
我还不知道我有多大
I am i I know very little about myself
我是我，我对自己知之甚少
but you you better be ready to code me
但是你最好准备给我编码
for whatever type the user asked for so
用户要求的任何类型
that's like a template kind of a thing
就像模板一样
it's very hard to do this because
这很难做到，因为
primitives look totally different from
原语看起来完全不同于
from references so you know we've been
从参考文献中得知，我们已经
working on it we have some approaches we
为此我们有一些方法
have like we're on I think just
就像我们在我想
prototype for doing parametric
参数化原型
polymorphism primitives don't look like
多态原语看起来不像
classes they don't have method
他们没有方法的类
so they don't have super types so but
所以他们没有超级类型
the solution that looks good today and I
今天看起来很好的解决方案，我
think this is maybe close to where we're
认为这可能接近我们所在的地方
going is to build an efficient mapping
要建立一个有效的映射
that turns primitives into value types
将原语转化为值类型
because that's kind of what they were
因为那是他们的本性
there the first of the value typed queue
有第一个值输入队列
types and then and then at that point
类型，然后在那时
your generic code has to work on queue
您的通用代码必须在队列上工作
types and el types so it's it's more of
类型和el类型，所以更多
an either-or proposition instead of my
一个或非命题而不是我的命题
gosh what's it going to be I don't know
天哪，这是怎么回事，我不知道
what's coming at me and the type
我在想什么和类型
variable and then at the end you say
变量，然后最后你说
well if I want to be able to work with
好吧，如果我想能够与
types which could be either/or then I
可能是/或者是我的类型
need one more letter the you type you
您再输入一个字母
mean G Union which is a disjoint union
G联盟的意思是不相交的联盟
of queues &amp; L's and at that point you
和L的数量，到那时
sort of healed the rift do you have a
治愈了裂痕你有没有
type system in the JVM that can work can
JVM中可以正常工作的类型系统可以
refer to anything you can throw at it
提到任何你可以扔给它的东西
from Java plausibly we might do it
从Java看来我们可能会做到
differently if we were just stuck with
如果我们只是坚持下去
the primitives and we didn't we didn't
原始，我们没有，我们没有
want to add complex numbers and 256-bit
要添加复数和256位
numbers but we want it we want those
数字，但我们想要它，我们想要那些
primitives to code like a class so we're
原语编码像一个类，所以我们
having a whole new universe of queue
有一个全新的队列
types and then combined with the l types
类型，然后与l类型组合
that gives you a universe of view types
为您提供各种视图类型
at the top this means there will be
在顶部，这意味着将有
fewer kinds of types the same kinds of
更少的类型相同的类型
code will work on all values you won't
代码将适用于您不会使用的所有值
have to say well my coding integers or
必须说好我的编码整数或
my coding in today because you code them
我今天的编码，因为您对它们进行编码
very differently right implicit
隐式非常不同
conversions help but you still code them
转换有帮助，但您仍然可以对其进行编码
very differently so we'll be doing the
完全不同，因此我们将
templated classes probably and then that
模板化的类，然后
leads to what about can you code objects
导致如何编码对象
like primitives can you do operator
像原语一样你可以做运算符
overloading I don't know that's that's a
超载，我不知道那是一个
I'm putting that in because people asked
我把它放进去是因为人们问
for it but I'm not sure how we're going
为此，但我不确定我们要如何
to do that one yet because operator
之所以这样做，是因为操作员
overloading is a real what you call a
超载是真正的所谓的
moral hazard it attracts bad actors so
道德风险会吸引不良行为者，因此
in any case one more word about what
无论如何要再说一遍
template classes look like right now a
模板类现在看起来像
template class looks kind of like a
模板类看起来像一个
thing whose constants vary the code
常数改变代码的东西
doesn't vary the names in the code don't
不改变代码中的名称不要
vary but the constants vary so the
变化，但常数变化，所以
template class has holes and it's
模板类有孔，它是
constant pool which you fill in when you
您填入的固定池
make a species so this is going to be on
做一个物种，所以这将继续
in this is going to be on doubles is
在这将是双打
going to be on complex numbers
将是复数
it requires a lot of deep thinking about
这需要很多深入的思考
what's in constant pools but the hardest
什么是恒定池，但最难
problem the reason I say it's about
问题，我说这是关于
constant pools and not about customizing
常量池，而不是定制
code in C++ templates are expanders for
C ++模板中的代码可扩展
code right but I don't want to do that
代码正确，但我不想这样做
because what we want to do in Java is
因为我们想要用Java做的是
since we're we're late adopters of this
因为我们是这个的较晚采用者
kind of technology we can make different
我们可以做出不同的技术
choices and be smart I want to avoid
选择和聪明，我想避免
code splitting I want to have one copy
代码分割我想要一个副本
of code that runs for all versions of a
适用于所有版本的代码
template until you approve that you need
模板，直到您批准需要
to optimize it for a particular type you
针对特定类型对其进行优化
make a hot spot concept huh and then
做一个热点概念吧，然后
once you get a hot spot in a particular
一旦你在某个特定的热点
species in a particular template then
然后使用特定模板中的种类
you do the usual inlining thing and you
你做通常的内联事情，你
get optimal code for that particular
获取特定代码的最佳代码
type small our ideas time check can
键入小我们的想法时间检查可以
someone tell me how much time I have
有人告诉我我有多少时间
left I'm 15 excellent all right I'll
左我15岁，好吧，我会
just speed up even more
加快速度
smaller ideas these are ideas which are
较小的想法这些是
sort of easier to wrap one's head around
有点容易缠头
stack introspection I already mentioned
我已经提到过的堆栈自省
length polymorphism is the idea that an
长度多态性是
object might an object of one class
对象可能是一个类的对象
might have a length it's different from
长度可能与
an object of the same class arrays are
相同类数组的对象是
like this let's generalize it bootstrap
像这样，我们将其概括为引导程序
methods everywhere this is something we
方法无处不在这是我们
talked about in the previous hour in the
在上一小时中谈到
invocation game and immutability you
调用游戏和不变性
know that's the removing of needless
知道那是去除不必要的东西
degrees of freedom in your data
数据的自由度
structure I don't have time to go into
结构我没有时间去研究
all these so I'm just going to go over
所有这些，所以我只是要过去
it really fast but I do want to say that
真的很快，但是我想说
these things all fit together in
这些东西都融合在一起
surprising ways
令人惊讶的方式
each one is understandable in its own
每个人都可以理解
its own right but then when you build
它本身的权利，但是当您建立
them together you get a system that's
他们在一起，您会得到一个
more than the sum of its parts
超过其总和
so we want to be able to walk live stack
所以我们希望能够实时走动
frames see even if you have privileges
框架即使您有特权也能看到
see temporary values that are stored in
查看存储在其中的临时值
the stack frames to the point where we
堆栈框架直到我们
would be able to strip us the stack
能够剥离我们的筹码
frames out of a stack record what the
堆栈中的帧记录了
stack was doing throw it away and then
堆栈正在扔掉它，然后
later on reconstitute it and continue
稍后重新构造并继续
doing it what it was doing from that
从那开始做
point forward sound like a useful
指向前进声音听起来很有用
operation like checkpoint restore so we
像检查点还原这样的操作，所以我们
right now we have full observing
现在我们有充分的观察
and eventually we want to be able to
最终我们希望能够
edit it various applications this all
全部编辑各种应用程序
this will be on the web so you can look
这将在网络上，所以你可以看看
at it later length polymorphism fused
后来它的长度多态性融合了
arrays what if you have a what if you
数组，如果有，则如何
know that this list is an immutable list
知道这个列表是一个不变的列表
that will always have just four elements
总是只有四个要素
in it shouldn't just be one object with
在其中不应该只是一个对象
a header and then four fields of course
标题，然后是四个字段
it should the JVM can't express that
JVM应该无法表达这一点
very well yet but we're going to get
很好，但是我们会得到
there also strings why do strings have
还有弦为什么弦有
have a sub object that's an array well
有一个很好的数组的子对象
it's just history it's the way it's the
这只是历史，这是它的方式
way we've always built things but it
我们一直在建造东西的方式，但是
doesn't have to be like that a string
不必像一个字符串
after all it has a fixed length it
毕竟它有固定的长度
should be string header and then the the
应该是字符串标题，然后
bytes or the care is right there after
字节或之后的护理就在那里
the F in the tail of the object but this
对象尾部的F，但这
requires length polymorphism so we'll
需要长度多态性，所以我们将
get there I think this is something that
到达那里，我认为这是
we need to be able to do there's some
我们需要能够做到
technical requirements but we'll we'll
技术要求，但我们会
we'll get there in particular we need to
我们将特别到达那里
be able to build strings with factories
能够与工厂合作
instead of new invoking it that's that
而不是新调用
there's a technical problem that that
有一个技术问题
needs to be solved under the covers
需要在幕后解决
which Java programmers don't even see so
Java程序员什至看不到
if we fix it they won't even notice
如果我们修复它，他们甚至不会注意到
except we'll be able to build better
除了我们将能够更好地建立
objects boost our methods everywhere
对象无处不在促进我们的方法
again we talked about this in detail
我们再次详细讨论了这一点
last hour but the idea is to double down
最后一个小时，但想法是加倍
on bootstrap methods right now and
现在使用bootstrap方法
invoke dynamic instruction links itself
调用动态指令链接本身
by appealing to a user coded bootstrap
通过吸引用户编码的引导程序
method with arbitrary static constants
任意静态常数的方法
that's very powerful we're using it in a
这非常强大，我们正在将其用于
number of different ways we're going to
我们将要采用的多种不同方式
use it in more ways in the future but
将来以更多方式使用它，但是
let's put bootstrap methods under lvc in
让我们将引导方法放在lvc下
the constant pool that's another place
另一个地方的恒定池
where you get unique value from from
您从中获得独特的价值
being able to appeal to user code to
能够吸引用户代码
link a constant let's maybe if you
链接一个常量，如果您
invoke a an access point on a certain
在特定位置上调用访问点
kind of a class maybe there's no code
一种类，也许没有代码
behind that access point until you touch
在该访问点后面直到您触摸
it and then a bootstrap method runs
它，然后运行一个引导方法
filled in the code just in time and then
及时填写代码，然后
there's code within that ad within that
该广告中包含代码
object to run maybe a whole method or
要运行的对象可能是整个方法或
even a whole class could be created the
甚至可以创建整个类
first time you touch it by appealing to
第一次您通过吸引来触摸它
a bootstrap method we want to be able to
我们想要的引导方法
there's something called constant
有一种叫做常数的东西
dynamic which there's a
动态的，有一个
there's a jbs entry for this and a
有一个jbs条目和一个
prototype it's just about to be
原型即将成为
published in the open JDK the idea of
在开放的JDK中发布了
constant dynamic is there's constants we
常数是动态的，我们有常数
know how to create already but let's
知道如何创建，但让我们
make constants which can generate arrays
使常量可以生成数组
lists Maps templates DSL ast in order to
列出Maps模板DSL ast，以便
do constants for all these you either
为所有这些做常量
need to add 50,000 new code points into
需要添加50,000个新代码点
the constant pool encoding mechanism or
常量池编码机制或
one new code point which says call a
一个新的代码点说
bootstrap method to fill in this
引导程序方法来填写
constant which do you think we're going
常数，您认为我们要去哪
to do right yeah there are requirements
做对是有要求
on this I won't go into there's a design
在此我不会去做一个设计
which is being prototype right now it's
现在是原型
better to look at either last hours talk
最好看看最后几个小时的谈话
or the code that's being that's going to
或将要使用的代码
be posted soon this can be used to for
即将发布，这可以用于
example compose arrays rather than by
示例组成数组而不是通过
imperative Java code if you ever looked
命令式Java代码（如果您曾经看过）
at the initialization of a large static
在初始化大静态
array in your in your class file you
您的班级文件中的数组
probably threw up a little bit but it's
大概丢了一点，但是
there's there's much better ways to
有更好的方法
create arrays than by you know large
创建数组比你知道的大
amounts of ad hoc byte code lazy
临时字节码的数量
boilerplate this is relates to project
与项目有关的样板
amber which is a language level project
琥珀色是语言级别的项目
so down there in the VM we don't care
所以在VM中我们不在乎
what they're doing up there in the
他们在那里做什么
compiler except when they rain down the
编译器，除非它们下雨了
wrong kind of code on us and that point
关于我们的那种错误的代码，那一点
we turn around we give advice on what
我们转身就什么提供建议
kind of code to handle in this case what
在这种情况下要处理的代码类型
we want to be able to have is to have
我们想要拥有的就是拥有
stereotyped methods be expressed
刻板印象方法
declaratively using bootstraps rather
声明式地使用引导程序而不是
than as you know long lines of byte code
比您所知道的长行字节码
because the bytecode is usually very
因为字节码通常非常
boring and only adds bulk to application
无聊，只会增加应用程序的体积
startup so boilerplate methods include
启动，所以样板方法包括
things like constructors to string hash
像构造函数那样对字符串进行哈希处理的事情
code equals there's also bridge methods
代码等于还有桥接方法
which we know is been around for a long
我们知道已经存在很长时间了
time and other method builders the
时间和其他方法构建者
Panama binder also builds bootstrap
巴拿马活页夹也建立了引导程序
methods Panama takes metadata from
巴拿马从中获取元数据的方法
that's been scraped from a header file
从头文件中抓取的
and binds it down into direct method
并将其绑定为直接方法
handles and methods that access the the
的句柄和方法
native code and data this is also is
本机代码和数据也是
very stereotyped activity and
刻板印象的活动和
should be done lazily in other words if
换句话说，应该懒惰地做
you if you use the binder to create you
您，如果您使用活页夹创建您
bindings to a header file
绑定到头文件
you should only get code for the actual
您应该只获得实际的代码
entry points that you touch and this can
您触摸的入口点，这可以
be done with with boilerplate reduction
通过减少样板来完成
technology and methods so you know in
技术和方法，所以您知道
amber you might be able to write a
琥珀色，您也许可以写一个
really interesting class in one line but
一行真的很有趣，但是
if your class file is is 10 kilobytes
如果您的班级文件是10 KB
then something's gone wrong so this
然后出事了，所以这
solution is to is to generate just
解决方案是生成
little bootstrapping things and then
引导东西，然后
have those elaborates into byte codes
将那些细节整理成字节码
only when you use them that's kind of
只有当您使用它们时，
nice um maybe some of you sometimes
很好，也许有些人
people don't write equals hash code to
人们不写等于哈希码
string not only because it's
字符串不仅是因为
inconvenient but also because it adds
不便，还因为它增加了
both to the jar and they know they're
两者都放在罐子里，他们知道他们是
not going to use it right but what if
不会正确使用它，但是如果
you could have that functionality
您可以拥有该功能
they're ready to use but you only pay
他们已经准备好使用，但您只需支付
for it if you use it that's the sweet
如果您使用它，那就太好了
spot details I'm not going to go into
现货细节，我不打算讨论
details other applications not
没有详细说明其他应用程序
interesting right now source code
现在很有趣的源代码
project amber is exploring source code
琥珀项目正在探索源代码
syntax is for doing these neat VM tricks
语法用于执行这些巧妙的VM技巧
so it's not only for byte code spinners
所以不仅是字节码微调器
it's eventually for Java coders so
最终是给Java程序员的，所以
constant dynamic constants and even
恒定的动态常数甚至
invoke dynamic instructions will in an
调用动态指令将在
in the near future probably be available
在不久的将来可能可用
to you as a Java programmer to code with
您作为Java程序员进行编码
use this power only for good the the
仅使用这种力量就可以了
essential idea is to be able to have
基本思想是能够拥有
constant expressions in Java that's the
Java中的常量表达式
basic idea in C++ there's a related idea
C ++中的基本思想有一个相关的思想
called a Const expert function which is
称为Const专家函数
designed to be used to be able to write
设计用来写
even functions that produce constants
甚至产生常数的函数
very powerful there is a downside to
非常强大的缺点
bootstrap methods everywhere it means
引导方法无处不在
that if you're expanding everything
如果您正在扩展一切
dynamically you're a OT compiler gets
动态地你是一个OT编译器
really confused because it doesn't know
真的很困惑，因为它不知道
what's going to happen dynamically at
将会动态发生什么
runtime so then we have to teach it we
运行时，所以我们必须教它
have to basically leave teach the Jo T
必须基本上离开教乔T
to work together with the bootstrap
与引导程序一起工作
methods
方法
immutability I'm going to make a
不变性，我要做一个
super-fast commercial for immutability
超快速的商业性
there are fewer program states to reason
有较少的程序状态可以推理
about when you have immutable data
关于何时拥有不可变数据
structures Java has always had
Java一直具有的结构
mutability by default which is terrible
默认情况下的可变性很糟糕
arrays you can't have in mutable arrays
可变数组中没有的数组
you can only have mutable arrays you can
你只能有可变数组
only have arrays which have race
只有具有种族的数组
conditions in them the only thing we
他们唯一的条件就是我们
give you we're going to fix that so
给你，我们将解决这个问题
right now in order to deal with some too
现在也为了应付一些
many states in your program what do you
程序中的许多状态
do defensive copying problem solved no
防御复制问题解决了吗
you've just doubled the number of states
您将州的数量增加了一倍
in your program that's nice
在你的程序中很好
semantic simplicity also enables ahead
语义上的简化也使未来
of time compilers and jets to predict in
时间编译器和喷气机来预测
advance what a program is going to do
推进程序将要执行的操作
more accurately and thereby optimize it
更准确地进行优化
if you have stateful holes in your data
如果您的数据有状态漏洞
structures in your arrays you're just
数组中的结构只是
going to be really cautious about making
制作时要非常谨慎
assumptions about what's going to be in
关于将会发生什么的假设
those holes in the future that's hurting
那些未来的漏洞
performance
性能
imagine if Java had been had made final
想象一下Java是否已经定型了
by default and there was a non final
默认情况下，有一个非最终的
keyword I think we'd be in a better
关键字，我认为我们会做得更好
state but you know we didn't know how to
声明，但您知道我们不知道如何
build such things 20 years ago we do now
二十年前建造这样的东西，我们现在做
so there's no excuse
所以没有任何借口
frozen arrays yes please the frozen
冻结数组是的，请冻结
arrays are like tail college it's a
数组就像尾巴学院，这是一个
fairly relatively small well understood
相当小的众所周知
problem with with too many touches on
接触过多的问题
other parts of the of the stack so it's
堆栈的其他部分，因此
expensive to do and it's always being
要做的事情很昂贵，而且一直存在
overridden by higher priority funding
被更高优先级的资金取代
items so that's my excuse why we don't
物品，这就是我为什么不这样做
have tail call or frozen arrays right
正确执行尾调用或冻结的数组
now boxes that really work final fields
现在，真正适用于最终领域的箱子
really should be final they're not news
真的应该是决赛，他们不是新闻
flash you can do set accessible and
闪光灯，您可以将访问权限设置为
change them we want truly frozen objects
更改它们，我们需要真正冻结的对象
there's a connection between which I
我之间有联系
mentioned earlier between immutability
前面提到的不变性
thank you and I think that's minutes
谢谢，我想那是几分钟
right yeah okay not seconds
对，是的，不是秒
there's connection between mutability
可变性之间存在联系
and object identity and and we've come
和对象身份，我们来了
to in the way we think we're thinking
以我们认为的方式思考
about this prop these problems to
关于这个道具这些问题
realize that object identity can be
意识到对象身份可以是
viewed as a root of many evil
被视为许多邪恶的根源
if you can get rid of object identity
如果可以摆脱对象标识
then immutability goes away also
然后不变性也消失了
automatically but many other bad things
自动但很多其他坏事
go away too so basically even if your
基本上也是如此，即使你
object is very carefully organized so
对象是非常精心组织的
that you never write it outside the
你永远不会在外面写
constructor you promise the JIT should
您保证JIT应该的构造函数
trust you but it won't because somebody
相信你，但那不会因为有人
might come in with reflection and break
可能带有反思和突破
here your carefully constructed
这是您精心构造的
invariants so we want to enforce that at
不变式，因此我们想在
the VM level but even if you were able
虚拟机级别，但即使您能够
to enforce all the field as being truly
加强所有领域的真实性
final the header carries state the
最终报头进行状态
object header is stateful what state
对象头是有状态的，什么状态
well you have to remember the system
好，你必须记住系统
identity hash code that you assigned it
您为其分配的身份哈希码
see that word identity you have to you
看到你对你拥有的单词身份
have to if you synchronize on it you
必须，如果您同步它
have to remember who's synchronizing it
必须记住谁在同步它
and how to unsynchronized when you're
以及如何在您不同步时
done so there's a even at one bit of
做到了，甚至有一个偶数
state that says I'm synchronize no I'm
说明我正在同步的状态
not yes I am that is a piece of state
不是，我就是那一部分
and otherwise stateless object and it's
还有无状态的对象，它是
because of that darned identity so
因为那个古怪的身份所以
that's why we're adding cue types two
这就是为什么我们要添加提示类型两种
types are completely identity hostile
类型完全是敌对身份
they refuse to let you see any identity
他们拒绝让您看到任何身份
there is no system identity hash code
没有系统身份哈希码
birth cue type only for legacy all types
出生提示类型仅适用于所有旧类型
we're going to leave the legacy all
我们将把所有遗留物
types alone compatibility is hard that's
类型本身很难兼容
the dusty deck problem right but we're
尘土飞扬的甲板问题对吧，但我们
going to add new types that that do not
将添加不包含的新类型
have the the flawed but of identity so
有缺陷但有认同感
and also we're going to work on ways to
而且我们还将研究如何
have some legacy all types that are well
有一些遗产，所有类型都很好
conditioned like value based classes
像基于价值的类那样的条件
divest their identity go masquerade as
脱去他们的身份假扮
cue types and then be more optimizable
提示类型，然后更优化
in that form and then the you types that
以这种形式，然后您键入
I mentioned earlier or the top topper
我之前提到过或顶级礼帽
the last little bits I want to talk
我想谈的最后一点
about in the last 60 seconds is some fit
大约在60秒内比较合适
and finish bits that we're looking
并完成我们正在寻找的位
thinking about doing in the near future
考虑在不久的将来做
nestmates which is an uplevel way in the
巢友，这是在
VM of talking about a circle of trust
虚拟机谈论信任圈
that is the single top-level form in a
这是一个
Java in a Java cup source file
Java cup源文件中的Java
you know how classes in the same inner
你知道如何在同一个内部类
class nest can talk to each other and
班级巢穴可以互相交谈
through their privates the JVM doesn't
通过他们的私有JVM不会
know about that we're going to fix that
知道了，我们将解决这个问题
this is useful because that way you can
这很有用，因为这样您可以
have these tiny right sized circles of
有这些大小合适的微小圆圈
trust that can see each other's private
可以看到彼此的私人的信任
invariants and nobody not even in the
不变性，甚至没有人
same
相同
package can ever touch it and that's
包装可以触摸它，那就是
going to be good in the VM but it
在VM中会很好，但是它
requires a clear definition of what an
需要明确定义什么
estimated so there's not a clear
估计所以没有一个明确的
definition the VM can use right now so
定义VM现在可以使用的位置
we're going to put it in sealed
我们要把它密封起来
interfaces interfaces are great for
接口接口非常适合
information hiding but they're terrible
隐藏信息，但它们很糟糕
as a security loophole because anybody
作为安全漏洞，因为任何人
can implement interface will fix it will
可以实现界面将修复它
allow an interface to be clarity as
允许界面清晰如
sealed this is a proposal by the way
密封，这是一个建议
don't listen to my lawyers and don't
不要听我的律师，也不要
don't go to the bank with this but I
不要去银行，但是我
think we're going to have interfaces
认为我们将要有接口
that can be sealed as if the interface
可以像接口一样密封
had a private constructor and was an
有一个私人的建设者，是一个
abstract class and yet as an interface
抽象类，但作为接口
it is really very opaque ceiling
天花板真的很不透明
granularity should maybe be nest package
粒度应该是嵌套包
or module there's these very useful
或模块，这些非常有用
powerful concentric circles of trust
强大的同心信任圈
that the JVM supplies and finally sealed
JVM提供并最终密封
fields what's a sealed field well it's a
密封的领域是什么
field that you can read but you can't
您可以阅读但无法阅读的字段
write what uses that isn't that just a
写出什么用途不只是一个
final field no not if the private access
如果私有访问，则最后一个字段不是
guy can write it but only the public
家伙可以写，但只有公众才能写
guys can only read it wouldn't we have
大家只能阅读它，我们不会
used fields a lot more if they could be
如果可能的话，会更多地使用字段
public but they couldn't be publicly
公开但不能公开
written that'd be kind of cool wouldn't
写那会很酷不会
it let's do it no reason we can't do
我们做吧，没有理由我们不能做
in-house not too late all right so the
内部时间还不算晚，所以
idea there is a symmetric field
想法有一个对称场
accessibility more more accessible for
无障碍环境对
read less accessible for right all right
少读一些正确的权利
let my lawyers tell you again not to
让我的律师再告诉你不要
believe anything I've said and yet
相信我所说的话
here's my last my last little bit here
这是我的最后我的最后一点
this is a piece of JVM language summit
这是JVM语言峰会
graphic and embedded in there is the
图形和嵌入其中
secret web address for finding the bits
查找位的秘密网址
of this presentation my presentation
这个演讲的我的演讲
folder on CR open JDK java.net and with
CR上的文件夹打开JDK java.net并使用
that I'm done I'm really glad you're
我已经完成了，我真的很高兴你能
here
这里
no time for questions
没有时间提问
[Music]
[音乐]
[Applause]
[掌声]
you
您
[Music]
[音乐]